=== WP Twitter ===
Plugin Name: WP Twitter
Contributors: fdoromo
Donate link: https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&hosted_button_id=Z9SRNRLLDAFZJ
Tags: twitter,twit, tweet, tweets, twitter widget, dynamic twitter widget, auto refresh tweet, twitter goodies,twitter tools, yourls, short url, shortlink, shorturl, Widget, Twitter , Post, Tweet, Integrate, Update, Sidebar, Sharethis 
Requires at least: 3.0
Tested up to: 3.4.2
Stable tag: 3.7
License: GPLv2 or later

Is a plugin that creates a complete integration between your WordPress blog and your Twitter account including ShareThis Buttons and Goodies Widgets.

== Description ==
[WP Twitter](http://fabrix.net/wp-twitter/ "Ver esta pagina em Portugues (pt-BR)") is a plugin that creates a complete integration between your WordPress blog and your Twitter account by giving you the following functionality:

* It will post a tweet when you have created a new post on your Wordpress blog and when you have updated a post.
* Complete Sharethis Button Integration
* Add Twitter Goodies to any Pages, Posts and Widget area.

Add both widgets into sidebar - Go to Appearance -> Widgets -> WP Twitter

to add Twitter Profile widget on page/post `[--wp_twitter--]`

to add Twitter Search Widget on page/post `[--wp_twitter_search--]`

Sharethis Button Option: Activate integration option from Admin Panel


The following short url services are supported:

* [YOURLS](http://yourls.org/)
* TinyURL 
* is.gd
* Bit.ly
* and Wordpress default URL format `Ex: domain.com/?p=123`

= Languages Available =
* English (default)
* Brazilian Portuguese (Português Brasileiro: pt_BR) translation by [Fabrix DoRoMo](http://fabrix.net)
* French (Français: fr_FR) translation by [Karim El Khalifa](http://www.moutons.ch/)
* Spanish (Español: es_ES) translation by [Juan Pablo Población Paredes](http://www.juventudfuenla.com/)
* Italian (Italiano: it_IT) translation by [TheShark_76]

= How To Contribute =
We'd love for you to get involved. Whatever your level of skill or however much time you can give, your contribution is greatly appreciated.

* **Users** - download the latest development version of the plugin, and submit bug/feature requests.

* **Non-English Speaking Users** - Contribute a translation using the GlotPress web interface - no technical knowledge required ([how to](http://translate.fabrix.net/projects/wp-twitter)).

* **Developers** - Fork the development version and submit a pull request, especially for any known issues


== Screenshots ==
1. URL Shortener Account Settings
2. ShareThis Button Integration
3. Widget Real-time Settings


== Installation ==
1. Upload the `wp-twitter` folder to your `/wp-content/plugins/` directory
1. Activate the `WP Twitter` plugin in your WordPress admin `Plugins`
1. Go to the `WP Twitter Options page` (Options > WP Twitter >) to set your Twitter account information.
1. Go to `Presentation / Widgets` in your WordPress admin area.
1. Drag the `WP Twitter` widget to your sidebar.



== Frequently Asked Questions ==

= Does WP Twitter require cURL? =
* Yes, WP Twitter requires the cURL utility.
Fortunately, this utility is a standard inclusion with PHP and virtually all users should experience no issues. If it does pose a problem, the link above will lead to further information to fix the problem.

= Does this plugin work with PHP4? =
No, this plugin does not work with php4.


== Changelog ==
* 3.7
    * Add Italian (Italiano: it_IT) translation by [TheShark_76]
    * Improvement of performance 
    * Various cosmetic fixes

* 3.6.2
    * Add Spanish (Español: es_ES) translation by [Juan Pablo Población Paredes](http://www.juventudfuenla.com/)

* 3.6.1
    * Various cosmetic fixes
    * Add French (Français: fr_FR) translation by [Karim El Khalifa](http://www.moutons.ch/)

* 3.6
    * ShareThis, support for change order or modify buttons.
    
* 3.5
    * Adds Brazilian Portuguese translation.
    * Bug Fix (ShareThis Button Integration).
    * ShareThis, added support for Bottom Fixed bar.

* 3.4 
    * ShareThis, added support for CopyNShare, ShareNow: enabled option to choosing a different theme. 

* 3.3 
    * ShareThis, added support for: ShareNow, Share Egg and Bars (Float Left/Right Side, Top of Page - scrolls down)  

* 3.2 
    * Bug Fix (ShareThis Button Integration)


* 3.1
    * Added the uninstaller
    * Added integration with ShareThis
    * Added Real-time widget config

* 3.0.1
    *  Bug Fix

* 3.0
    *  Completely NEW version (new core, old version was discontinued <2.5)

* 2.5
    * Added WP 2.9+ compatibility and tweaks


* 2.4
    * BookMarklet: added search on twitter


* 2.3
    * Add: Set your URL shortening
    * bug fix: space at the end of the prefix


* 2.2.1
    * Russian translation (ru_RU)

* 2.2
    * Added the WordPress login page in BookMarklet. Note: only the administrator login has access.

* 2.1
    * Turn on or off in each post

* 2.0
    * Completely new version, including the BookMarklet

* 1.5
    * Compatibility with WordPress 2.8

* 1.4

    * New Admin Screens Layout, included Yours last tweets
    * Add avatar in Widget front end

* 1.3
    * bug fix: installation code was failing on some systems

* 1.2
    * Settings : verify credentials

* 1.1
    * Multilanguage support

* 1.0
    * Initial release